downtown retail apocalypse.
City policies contradict.
Walgreens closing one by one.
Target locks up everything.
Smash and grab.
It's all the rage.
Organized theft takes center stage.
Billionaire tax breaks abound.
While mom and pop shops hit the ground.
Professor politics regresses hopes.
Buffering planning built on false cloaks The city by the bay of disarray Astithesis continue to fade away Empty storefronts line the streets Diabolism in retreat Corporate chains all running scared While City Hall just stares and stares Bye bye bye Watch them go Bye bye bye Told you so
Security guards with hands all tied A shoplifter's run outside Five-finger discount, daily thrill What consequence does equal nil?
Tech bros paid three grand for rent While small shops can't make a dent Economic paradox San Francisco's than Dora's box High-rise towers, port-a-tours What the hell are we fighting for?
Social experiment gone wrong
That's the theme of this gap song.
Leftists aren't going to try in the seats.
Capitalism in the dreef.
Corporate chains aren't running scared.
While City Hall just stands and stares.
Bye bye bye.
Watch them go.
Told you so.